<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <!-- EN:
    <li>questDescription->Your radio lights up with another request for E352. The automated satellite tells you of another vault, lurking somewhere in the distance. This vault is marked one of many in a series of "seized vaults", where supersoldier patients sealed off the genetic monstrosities underground. \n\nThe site briefing attatched reads as follows:\n[story]\n\n The satellite wants you to take care of the supersoldiers, then reopen the vault door. It refuses to elaborate on what the purpose of the mission is. Your only directive is to re-open the underground section of the vault. Once it has been unsealed, you may leave or loot the site for ancient technology.</li>
    <li>story->This vault's patients guard the exterior, after they heard rumors of letting the monstrosities roam free. Afraid for their descendants, they staged an uprising to stop the entire operation. They took out several doctors then rushed to seal the massive underground vault door. After some deliberation, a group of patients decided to remain at the site. Choosing to give their lives to ensure their captors don't return to unleash the horrors onto the world was their way of keeping their families safe.</li>
    <li>story->This vault contained a cult born from captivity. Through an experiment, a patient gained a powerful ability based around the external manipulation of the inner-self. He took it upon himself to thrust his ideology onto the other patients, until a unity of intention formed among the captives. They were to seize this site for themselves, and guard it as a beacon to their new leader. Executives heard this rumor, and chose to capture him. Strapped to machines, they numbed his synapses and attempted to remove his ability with experimental treatments. As the cult burst out of containment and stormed the halls, they were unaware of the state of their leader as they mercilessly took revenge on their captors. After escaping the underground vault, the members sealed the door and stood to guard their temple. It remains unclear whether the leader managed to escape, or became a monstrosity himself in their process of detainment.</li>
    <li>story->Those who surround the vault guard a terrible secret. A patient was given the remarkable ability of telepathy through an experiment. The doctors were shocked as the man divulged specific details about their private lives. After being placed with the other patients, it is said the telepath began to disturb them with his accuracy. He began to unearth intimate details about their personal affairs, and the secrets they kept buried. Things changed when he looked at a disheveled patient for too long and heard a piece of information too dark to bear. The patients arranged to have the telepath killed, but executives intervened. The telepath used that opportunity to read the layout of the vault from one of the doctor's thoughts, and unseal the vault door. As he and a handful of other patients reached the surface, the disheveled man kicked the telepath back downstairs into the vault. Him and the other patients agreed to keep him sealed there forever, guarding their buried secrets with the horrors underneath.</li>
    <li>story->This vault is guarded by a loyal group of friends. The underground halls once contained a gifted patient with the ability to manipulate her form. She could transform into anything on a whim. The doctors would bring out turtles and rabbits to test her skill, and through a painful melting process she was able to form a shell and become unmistakably a turtle. Overtime, this process became too grueling to tolerate. She was well-liked among the other patients, and they ended up taking great pity on her. On one night, they convinced the girl to melt into the form of a doctor to stage a breakout. She managed to bring all her friends to the vault door in her disguise, but was said to have instead accidentally unleashed a wave of the failed genetic horrors. The group of patients managed to escape, but the girl was left behind. Her friends now camp above the vault, hoping to one day rescue her from the depths. They speculate that the only way she could have survived is if she assumed the form of one of the monstrosities, forced to roam the halls masquerading as one of them.</li>
  -->
  <VQE_AncientResearchVault.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->Tu radio se ilumina con otra solicitud para E352. El satélite automatizado te habla de otra bóveda, acechando en algún lugar a lo lejos. Esta bóveda está marcada como una de las muchas en una serie de "bóvedas incautadas", donde los pacientes supersoldados sellaron las monstruosidades genéticas bajo tierra. \n\nEl informe del sitio adjunto dice lo siguiente:\n[story]\n\n El satélite quiere que te encargues de los supersoldados y luego vuelvas a abrir la puerta de la bóveda. Se niega a dar detalles sobre cuál es el propósito de la misión. Tu única directiva es volver a abrir la sección subterránea de la bóveda. Una vez que haya sido abierta, puedes irte o saquear el sitio en busca de tecnología antigua.</li>
    <li>story->Los pacientes de esta bóveda custodian el exterior, después de escuchar rumores de dejar que las monstruosidades deambulen libremente. Temiendo por sus descendientes, organizaron un levantamiento para detener toda la operación. Acabaron con varios doctores y luego se apresuraron a sellar la enorme puerta de la bóveda subterránea. Tras deliberar, un grupo de pacientes decidió permanecer en el lugar. Elegir dar sus vidas para asegurar que sus captores no regresen para desatar los horrores sobre el mundo fue su forma de mantener a sus familias a salvo.</li>
    <li>story->Esta bóveda contenía un culto nacido del cautiverio. A través de un experimento, un paciente obtuvo una poderosa habilidad basada en la manipulación externa del yo interior. Se encargó de imponer su ideología a los demás pacientes, hasta que se formó una unidad de intención entre los cautivos. Debían apoderarse de este sitio para ellos mismos y custodiarlo como un faro para su nuevo líder. Los ejecutivos escucharon este rumor y decidieron capturarlo. Atado a máquinas, adormecieron sus sinapsis e intentaron eliminar su habilidad con tratamientos experimentales. Mientras el culto salía de la contención y asaltaba los pasillos, no eran conscientes del estado de su líder mientras se vengaban despiadadamente de sus captores. Tras escapar de la bóveda subterránea, los miembros sellaron la puerta y se quedaron a custodiar su templo. No está claro si el líder logró escapar o si él mismo se convirtió en una monstruosidad en el proceso de detención.</li>
    <li>story->Quienes rodean la bóveda guardan un terrible secreto. A un paciente se le otorgó la notable habilidad de la telepatía a través de un experimento. Los doctores se sorprendieron cuando el hombre divulgó detalles específicos sobre sus vidas privadas. Tras ser colocado con los otros pacientes, se dice que el telépata comenzó a molestarlos con su precisión. Empezó a desenterrar detalles íntimos sobre sus asuntos personales y los secretos que mantenían enterrados. Las cosas cambiaron cuando miró a un paciente desaliñado durante demasiado tiempo y escuchó una información demasiado oscura para soportarla. Los pacientes planearon matar al telépata, pero los ejecutivos intervinieron. El telépata aprovechó esa oportunidad para leer el diseño de la bóveda de los pensamientos de uno de los doctores y abrir la puerta de la bóveda. Mientras él y un puñado de otros pacientes llegaban a la superficie, el hombre desaliñado pateó al telépata de vuelta al piso de abajo, a la bóveda. Él y los otros pacientes acordaron mantenerlo sellado allí para siempre, custodiando sus secretos enterrados con los horrores de abajo.</li>
    <li>story->Esta bóveda está custodiada por un grupo de amigos leales. Los pasillos subterráneos albergaron una vez a una paciente dotada con la habilidad de manipular su forma. Podía transformarse en cualquier cosa por capricho. Los doctores traían tortugas y conejos para probar su habilidad, y a través de un doloroso proceso de derretimiento era capaz de formar un caparazón y convertirse inequívocamente en una tortuga. Con el tiempo, este proceso se volvió demasiado agotador para tolerarlo. Era muy querida entre los demás pacientes, y terminaron sintiendo una gran lástima por ella. Una noche, convencieron a la chica de que se derritiera en la forma de un doctor para organizar una fuga. Logró llevar a todos sus amigos a la puerta de la bóveda con su disfraz, pero se dice que, en cambio, desató accidentalmente una oleada de horrores genéticos fallidos. El grupo de pacientes logró escapar, pero la chica se quedó atrás. Sus amigos ahora acampan sobre la bóveda, con la esperanza de rescatarla algún día de las profundidades. Especulan que la única forma en que podría haber sobrevivido es si asumió la forma de una de las monstruosidades, obligada a vagar por los pasillos haciéndose pasar por una de ellas.</li>
  </VQE_AncientResearchVault.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN:
    <li>questName(priority=1)->E352 - [verb] the seized [place]</li>
    <li>verb->Secure</li>
    <li>verb->Contain</li>
    <li>verb->Unseal</li>
    <li>place->lab</li>
    <li>place->vault</li>
    <li>place->site</li>
  -->
  <VQE_AncientResearchVault.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName(priority=1)->E352 - [verb] [place]</li>
    <li>verb->Asegurar</li>
    <li>verb->Contener</li>
    <li>verb->Abrir</li>
    <li>place->el laboratorio incautado</li>
    <li>place->la bóveda incautada</li>
    <li>place->el sitio incautado</li>
  </VQE_AncientResearchVault.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  
</LanguageData>