<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <!-- EN:
    <li>questDescription->Data retrieved from the ancient relay station confirms the crash site of the cryptoforge ship’s stern, located not far from the scanning facility. While this section does not contain the legendary cryptoforge itself, it holds a crucial black box. To pinpoint the final cryptoforge fragment, we must retrieve its data and pair it with the bow’s black box records. \n\nThe wreckage scan reveals a high concentration of dormant mechanoids aboard, making conflict likely. The ship’s hull is built from near-indestructible material, limiting possible entry points. Ancient airlocks might still be operational, though forcing them open will require effort. Some external turrets remain active, further complicating the approach. Inside, automated floor freezers keep the corridors at dangerously low temperatures, serving as a defensive measure against intruders. \n\nDespite these challenges, the wreckage contains valuable resources. Extracting as much salvage as possible will be essential for reactivating the cryptoforge and crafting the legendary cryptogear.\n\nAccording to the scan, the ship is protected by at least:\n[ListOfEnemies]</li>
  -->
  <VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter2.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->Los datos recuperados de la antigua estación de retransmisión confirman el lugar del impacto de la popa de la nave criptoforja, situada no lejos de la instalación de escaneo. Aunque esta sección no contiene la legendaria criptoforja en sí, alberga una caja negra crucial. Para localizar el fragmento final de la criptoforja, debemos recuperar sus datos y combinarlos con los registros de la caja negra de la proa. \n\nEl escaneo de los restos revela una alta concentración de mecanoides inactivos a bordo, lo que hace probable un conflicto. El casco de la nave está construido con un material casi indestructible, lo que limita los posibles puntos de entrada. Las esclusas de aire antiguas podrían seguir operativas, aunque forzarlas requerirá esfuerzo. Algunas torretas externas permanecen activas, lo que complica aún más la aproximación. En el interior, los congeladores de suelo automatizados mantienen los pasillos a temperaturas peligrosamente bajas, sirviendo como medida defensiva contra intrusos. \n\nA pesar de estos desafíos, los restos contienen recursos valiosos. Extraer todo el salvamento posible será esencial para reactivar la criptoforja y fabricar el legendario criptoequipo.\n\nSegún el escaneo, la nave está protegida por al menos:\n[ListOfEnemies]</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter2.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN:
    <li>questName->Cryptoforge stern</li>
  -->
  <VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter2.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Popa de la criptoforja</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter2.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  
</LanguageData>