<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <!-- EN:
    <li>questDescription->Data recovered from the ancient relay station has revealed the crash site of the cryptoforge ship’s bow, located not far from the scanning relay’s position. While this section does not house the cryptoforge itself, it contains a vital black box. To locate the final ship fragment, we must retrieve its data and pair it with the information from the stern’s black box. \n\nScans indicate a significant presence of insectoid lifeforms infesting the wreckage, making combat inevitable if we wish to reach the bridge where the black box is stored. The ship’s hull is composed of nearly indestructible material, limiting our means of entry. Some ancient airlocks may still function, but forcing them open will be necessary. A weak energy signature has also been detected within - likely from a dormant reactor. If reactivated, it may power the ship’s old floor heaters, weakening the cold-adapted insectoids inside.\n\nAlthough the cryptoforge itself is not housed within this wreckage, valuable resources remain, fused and reshaped by the ship’s violent descent. Extracting these materials will aid in restoring the cryptoforge and crafting the legendary cryptogear. Studying the black box should be our top priority.</li>
  -->
  <VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter3.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->Los datos recuperados de la antigua estación de retransmisión han revelado el lugar del impacto de la proa de la nave criptoforja, situada no lejos de la posición del repetidor de escaneo. Aunque esta sección no alberga la criptoforja en sí, contiene una caja negra vital. Para localizar el fragmento final de la nave, debemos recuperar sus datos y combinarlos con la información de la caja negra de la popa. \n\nLos escaneos indican una presencia significativa de formas de vida insectoides infestando los restos, lo que hace que el combate sea inevitable si deseamos llegar al puente donde se guarda la caja negra. El casco de la nave está compuesto de un material casi indestructible, lo que limita nuestros medios de entrada. Es posible que algunas esclusas de aire antiguas sigan funcionando, pero será necesario forzarlas para abrirlas. También se ha detectado una débil firma de energía en el interior, probablemente de un reactor inactivo. Si se reactiva, podría alimentar los antiguos calentadores de suelo de la nave, debilitando a los insectoides adaptados al frío que hay en su interior.\n\nAunque la criptoforja en sí no se encuentra dentro de estos restos, quedan recursos valiosos, fusionados y remodelados por el violento descenso de la nave. La extracción de estos materiales ayudará a restaurar la criptoforja y a fabricar el legendario criptoequipo. Estudiar la caja negra debe ser nuestra máxima prioridad.</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter3.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN:
    <li>questName->Cryptoforge bow</li>
  -->
  <VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter3.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Proa de la criptoforja</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter3.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  
</LanguageData>