<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <!-- EN: gauranlenkin -->
  <VRE_Gauranlenkin.label>gauranlenkin</VRE_Gauranlenkin.label>
  <!-- EN: Based on genetic data retrofitted from Gauranlen Inc.’s investment into dendrology following the Fall of Sorne, phytokins are plant-based humanoids with an emphasis on symmetry and symbiosis. Their ability to subsist only on sunlight and affinity with any and all plantlife make them especially suited to aiding newly established colonies or underperforming industrial farms.\n\nBased on research from the forest planet of Phytok that committed to extensive analysis on human-compatibility with psychic energy, phytokin xenogerms are typically exclusive to high-ranking, supporting roles in megacorporations and planetary governments. Their unique way of reproduction has resulted in many identical offspring, with each generation becoming successively more competent than their progenitor, further contributing to their extremely low numbers. Their affinity with plantlife, along with the side effect of extremely high and ever-increasing psychic sensitivity, mean that any phytokin xenohumans found on the Rim are always adapted to high-concept, dominant trees that are present on their residing planet.\n\nThis particular xenogerm has adapted itself to Gauranlen trees, allowing them to act as a non-stationary Dryad Queen, albeit without potential for growth. They can also improve attempts at connecting with a local Gauranlen tree as well as being twice as effective as a non-phytokin at pruning their own tree. -->
  <VRE_Gauranlenkin.description>Basado en datos genéticos readaptados de la inversión de Gauranlen Inc. en dendrología tras la Caída de Sorne, los fitokins son humanoides basados en plantas con énfasis en la simetría y la simbiosis. Su capacidad para subsistir solo con luz solar y su afinidad con toda la vida vegetal los hacen especialmente adecuados para ayudar a colonias recién establecidas o granjas industriales de bajo rendimiento.\n\nBasado en investigaciones del planeta forestal de Phytok que se comprometió a un análisis exhaustivo sobre la compatibilidad humana con la energía psíquica, los xenogérmenes fitokin son típicamente exclusivos de roles de apoyo de alto rango en megacorporaciones y gobiernos planetarios. Su forma única de reproducción ha resultado en mucha descendencia idéntica, con cada generación volviéndose sucesivamente más competente que su progenitor, contribuyendo aún más a sus números extremadamente bajos. Su afinidad con la vida vegetal, junto con el efecto secundario de una sensibilidad psíquica extremadamente alta y siempre creciente, significa que cualquier xenohumano fitokin encontrado en el Borde siempre está adaptado a árboles dominantes de alto concepto que están presentes en su planeta de residencia.\n\nEste xenogermen en particular se ha adaptado a los árboles Gauranlen, permitiéndoles actuar como una Reina Dríada no estacionaria, aunque sin potencial de crecimiento. También pueden mejorar los intentos de conexión con un árbol Gauranlen local, además de ser el doble de efectivos que un no fitokin al podar su propio árbol.</VRE_Gauranlenkin.description>
  <!-- EN: Powerful advisors to rulers and despots, gauranlenkins are beautiful and cunning and possess an ability to connect with a gauranlen tree, greatly enhancing its abilities. Gauranlenkins can spawn two dryads that will consider them their mother, and will obey their every command. They are excellent at taking care of plants and reproduce via planting a saplingchild. -->
  <VRE_Gauranlenkin.descriptionShort>Poderosos consejeros de gobernantes y déspotas, los gauranlenkins son hermosos y astutos y poseen la capacidad de conectarse con un árbol gauranlen, mejorando enormemente sus habilidades. Los gauranlenkins pueden engendrar dos dríadas que los considerarán su madre y obedecerán todas sus órdenes. Son excelentes cuidando plantas y se reproducen plantando un niño-brote.</VRE_Gauranlenkin.descriptionShort>
  
</LanguageData>