<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <!-- EN:
    <li>questDescription->Our intel allowed us to pinpoint the location of a shuttle staging post belonging to [empire_name]. These staging posts allow shuttles to refuel between destinations. Destroying it will greatly hinder the Empire’s ability to freely travel the planet and resupply their forward bases.\n\nWe may be able to trigger a chain detonation of the fuel containers to create havoc and make our job easier.\n\nWe might find some useful supplies scattered around the staging post. If we have the time, we should take what we can.\n\nThe shuttle staging post is protected by:\n[forces_description]\n\nWe have also been informed that the location is protected by a number of ground-mounted striker turrets. Despite the limited range, these turrets can easily reveal our approach and provide covering fire for the imperial army.\n\nThe staging post is protected by surveillance pillars. They should not be approached, and instead should be disabled from afar - either by destroying them, or cutting off their power. Once activated, they will greatly increase our visibility.\n\nThe objective of this assignment is to destroy all fuel containers. Once that is done, the reward will arrive and we will have to make our escape.\n\nOnce we arrive at the staging post, we can expect an imperial response if our visibility is high enough. We will only have a limited amount of time to complete the mission.</li>
  -->
  <VFED_ShuttleStagingPost.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->Nuestra inteligencia nos permitió localizar un puesto de escala de transbordadores perteneciente a [empire_name]. Estos puestos de escala permiten a los transbordadores repostar entre destinos. Destruirlo obstaculizará enormemente la capacidad del Imperio para viajar libremente por el planeta y reabastecer sus bases avanzadas.\n\nPodríamos provocar una detonación en cadena de los contenedores de combustible para crear caos y facilitar nuestro trabajo.\n\nPodríamos encontrar algunos suministros útiles dispersos por el puesto de escala. Si tenemos tiempo, deberíamos tomar lo que podamos.\n\nEl puesto de escala de transbordadores está protegido por:\n[forces_description]\n\nTambién se nos ha informado que la ubicación está protegida por varias torretas striker montadas en el suelo. A pesar de su alcance limitado, estas torretas pueden revelar fácilmente nuestra aproximación y proporcionar fuego de cobertura para el ejército imperial.\n\nEl puesto de escala está protegido por pilares de vigilancia. No deben acercarse a ellos, sino que deben desactivarse desde lejos, ya sea destruyéndolos o cortando su energía. Una vez activados, aumentarán enormemente nuestra visibilidad.\n\nEl objetivo de esta misión es destruir todos los contenedores de combustible. Una vez hecho esto, la recompensa llegará y tendremos que escapar.\n\nUna vez que lleguemos al puesto de escala, podemos esperar una respuesta imperial si nuestra visibilidad es lo suficientemente alta. Solo tendremos una cantidad limitada de tiempo para completar la misión.</li>
  </VFED_ShuttleStagingPost.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN:
    <li>questName->Shuttle staging post</li>
  -->
  <VFED_ShuttleStagingPost.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Puesto de escala de transbordadores</li>
  </VFED_ShuttleStagingPost.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    
</LanguageData>