<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <!-- EN:
    <li>questDescription->The intel we have gathered allowed us to gain insight into the location of a supply depot belonging to [empire_name]. Supply depots like that are often scattered around imperial settlements and serve as secure stockpiles for the most valuable resources. Keeping these supply depots hidden away discourages any raiders from attacking these settlements.\n\nThe compound is guaranteed to contain numerous supply crates. Stealing these items is bound to slow down the Imperial war effort.\n\nIt is also possible we will find additional Biosecured crates, which can only be opened by noble-born people.\n\nThe supply depot is protected by:\n[forces_description]\n\nThe compound is protected by surveillance pillars. They should not be approached, and instead should be disabled from afar - either by destroying them, or cutting off their power. Once activated, they will greatly increase our visibility.\n\nThe objective of this assignment is to open all supply crates in the area. Once that is done, the reward will arrive and we will have to make our escape.\n\nOnce we arrive at the compound, we can expect an imperial response if our visibility is high enough. We will only have a limited amount of time to complete the mission.</li>
  -->
  <VFED_SupplyDepotRaid.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->La inteligencia que hemos reunido nos permitió obtener información sobre la ubicación de un depósito de suministros perteneciente a [empire_name]. Depósitos de suministros como ese a menudo se encuentran dispersos alrededor de los asentamientos imperiales y sirven como reservas seguras para los recursos más valiosos. Mantener estos depósitos de suministros ocultos desalienta a los asaltantes de atacar estos asentamientos.\n\nEstá garantizado que el complejo contiene numerosas cajas de suministros. Robar estos artículos seguramente ralentizará el esfuerzo de guerra imperial.\n\nTambién es posible que encontremos cajas bioseguras adicionales, que solo pueden ser abiertas por personas de noble cuna.\n\nEl depósito de suministros está protegido por:\n[forces_description]\n\nEl complejo está protegido por pilares de vigilancia. No deben acercarse a ellos, sino que deben desactivarse desde lejos, ya sea destruyéndolos o cortando su energía. Una vez activados, aumentarán enormemente nuestra visibilidad.\n\nEl objetivo de esta misión es abrir todas las cajas de suministros en el área. Una vez hecho esto, la recompensa llegará y tendremos que escapar.\n\nUna vez que lleguemos al complejo, podemos esperar una respuesta imperial si nuestra visibilidad es lo suficientemente alta. Solo tendremos una cantidad limitada de tiempo para completar la misión.</li>
  </VFED_SupplyDepotRaid.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN:
    <li>questName->Supply depot raid</li>
  -->
  <VFED_SupplyDepotRaid.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Asalto al depósito de suministros</li>
  </VFED_SupplyDepotRaid.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    
</LanguageData>