<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <!-- EN:
    <li>questDescription->We have received the news of a techprinter installation belonging to [empire_name] near our location. Techprinters are a huge environmental hazard, and are used by techfriars to replicate their knowledge on techprints.\n\nTechite discs used in this process are extremely toxic and flammable. We might be able to ignite a stack of these discs and see the inferno unfold.\n\nThe techprinter installation is protected by:\n[forces_description].\n\nTwo palintone turrets are located at the installation. They are powerful, anti-infantry weapons firing large-caliber shells at incredible speeds, dealing heavy damage over significant ranges. Their ammo needs to be stored right next to them, and a precise shot might set off a chain explosion.\n\nWe have also been informed that the location is protected by a number of ground-mounted striker turrets. Despite the limited range, these turrets can easily reveal our approach and provide covering fire for the imperial army.\n\nTwo techfriars are most certainly at the installation. Killing them is not necessary.\n\nThe techprinter installation is protected by a number of surveillance pillars. They should not be approached, and instead should be disabled from afar - either by destroying them, or cutting off their power. Once activated, they will greatly increase our visibility.\n\nThe objective of this assignment is to destroy the techprinters by any means necessary. Once that is done, the reward will arrive and we will have to make our escape.\n\nOnce we arrive at the installation, we can expect an imperial response if our visibility is high enough. We will only have a limited amount of time to complete the mission.</li>
  -->
  <VFED_TechprinterDemolition.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->Hemos recibido noticias de una instalación de tecnoimpresoras perteneciente a [empire_name] cerca de nuestra ubicación. Las tecnoimpresoras son un gran peligro ambiental y son utilizadas por los tecnofrailes para replicar su conocimiento en tecnoimpresiones.\n\nLos discos de tecnita utilizados en este proceso son extremadamente tóxicos e inflamables. Podríamos encender una pila de estos discos y ver cómo se desata el infierno.\n\nLa instalación de tecnoimpresoras está protegida por:\n[forces_description].\n\nDos torretas palintone se encuentran en la instalación. Son armas poderosas anti-infantería que disparan proyectiles de gran calibre a velocidades increíbles, causando graves daños a distancias significativas. Su munición debe almacenarse justo al lado de ellas, y un disparo preciso podría provocar una explosión en cadena.\n\nTambién se nos ha informado que la ubicación está protegida por varias torretas striker montadas en el suelo. A pesar de su alcance limitado, estas torretas pueden revelar fácilmente nuestra aproximación y proporcionar fuego de cobertura para el ejército imperial.\n\nEs casi seguro que hay dos tecnofrailes en la instalación. Matarlos no es necesario.\n\nLa instalación de tecnoimpresoras está protegida por varios pilares de vigilancia. No deben acercarse a ellos, sino que deben desactivarse desde lejos, ya sea destruyéndolos o cortando su energía. Una vez activados, aumentarán enormemente nuestra visibilidad.\n\nEl objetivo de esta misión es destruir las tecnoimpresoras por cualquier medio necesario. Una vez hecho esto, la recompensa llegará y tendremos que escapar.\n\nUna vez que lleguemos a la instalación, podemos esperar una respuesta imperial si nuestra visibilidad es lo suficientemente alta. Solo tendremos una cantidad limitada de tiempo para completar la misión.</li>
  </VFED_TechprinterDemolition.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN:
    <li>questName->Techprinter demolition</li>
  -->
  <VFED_TechprinterDemolition.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Demolición de tecnoimpresoras</li>
  </VFED_TechprinterDemolition.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    
</LanguageData>